A.D.
M.
Due to its declining birthrate of the human popula- tion,
Akibat dari turunnya tingkat kelahiran populasi manusia,
this country has turned into a nation of cats.
negara ini menjadi negeri para kucing.
Cat Country Japan.
Negara Kucing Jepang.
My dad is too easy on Sora.
Ayahku terlalu memanjakan Sora.
Dad and Sora
Ayah dan Sora
There you go, Sora.
Nih, Sora.
Dad's giving him another snack…
Ayah memberinya camilan lagi…
He just ate, dad.
Dia baru saja makan, ayah.
But Sora was asking for it.
Tapi kan Sora yang minta.
I just really, really wanted it.
Aku terlanjur kepingin.
It can't be helped, right?
Mau gimana lagi, kan?
It can't be helped.
Mau gimana lagi.
If you keep spoiling him, he'll get bratty.
Kalau ayah manjain dia terus, nanti dia jadi benar-benar manja.
My dad always spoils Sora.
Ayah selalu memanjakan Sora.
It's fine for cats to be selfish. Right, Sora?
Kucing kan tidak apa-apa kalau terlalu manja. Iya, kan, Sora?
Being selfish is not good.
Terlalu manja itu tidak baik, loh.
What?
Eh?
He's quick to betray.
Dia sering mengingkarinya.
But, any more than this is not allowed.
Tapi enggak boleh lebih dari ini.
You'll get fat if you eat too much.
Nanti kamu jadi gemukan, karena kebanyakan makan.
What? Fat?
Apa? Gemuk?
Guess it can't be helped.
Ya… mau gimana lagi.
Dad?
Ayah?
Well, cats are still cute even if they're chubby, so a little…
Habisnya, kucing kan tetap lucu walaupun gemukan, jadi sedikit…
Still cute even if chubby?
Tetap lucu walau gemukan?
I see. So cats are still cute even when they're fat?
Oh, gitu. Jadi kucing tetap lucu walaupun gemukan?
Well, I guess so.
Yah, kurasa begitu.
In that case, eating a lot isn't so bad, is it?
Kalau gitu, makan banyak enggak apa-apa, dong?
It's bad for your health.
Enggak bagus buat kamu .
Well, my break is almost over.
Waktu istirahat Ayah sudah mau habis.
Alright, Sora. Dad's got to get back to work.
Oke, Sora. Ayah balik kerja lagi, ya.
Work?
Kerja?
My dad is easy on Sora, but…
Ayahku emang memanjakan Sora, tapi…
I suppose I could rest for just a bit more.
Kayaknya Ayah istirahat sebentar lagi, deh.
Sora is easy on my dad, too.
Sora juga memanjakan Ayah.
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe was utilized
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe diutilisasikan
: geckyzz
: geckyzz